videoelephant.com 2019-06-04

# VideoElephant | Privacy Policy

### Introduction

VideoElephant Limited (“we”, “us”, and “ours”) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. VideoElephant is an online B2B marketplace for long and short-form video content making content acquisition easy for web publishers, mobile operators, VOD, IPTV and broadcasters with our centralized marketplace. 

This Privacy Policy identifies the purposes for which personal information is collected, used and disclosed by us and sets out how we comply with our obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation and Data Protection Act 2018 (the “Acts”) and all other applicable laws. 

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

### What does Personal Data Mean?

In this Privacy Policy, the term “Personal Data” means data that identifies an individual such as, for example, your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. 

#####  What information do we collect? 

You can visit and browse our site without providing any Personal Data. You may voluntarily provide Personal Data, such as contact information or we may ask for such information in various forms on this site, including requests for product or service information or information from you as a registered Member. 

We may ask you for information when you report a problem with our site or our service. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. 

###  Navigational Information 

##### Cookies

Our site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our site and also allows us to improve our site. We use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize pages on our Websites, or register for the Subscription Service, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. When you return to the same Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the customized features. 

##### Log Files

We may collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites using log files that are not associated with your name or other personal information. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by us. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, internet service provider (ISP), the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, clickstream data, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by VideoElephant for the operation of the User Service, to maintain quality of the User Service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the VideoElephant Website. For these purposes, we do link this automatically-collected data to Personal Information such as name, email address, address, and phone number. 

##### Third Party Tracking Technologies

We may collect, and we allow third parties to collect, information about how you use and interact with our site such as for example Google Analytics. The use of cookies and web beacons by any tracking utility company is not covered by our Privacy Policy. 

### Opting out and Unsubscribing

##### Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information

Upon request VideoElephant will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Information. If you provide us with your Personal Information, you have the following rights with respect to that information: 

  * To review the user information that you have supplied to us 
  * To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us 
  * To request that your user information not be used to contact you 
  * To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use 
  * To request that your user information be deleted from our records
  * To opt out of being solicited by VideoElephant or third parties

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [privacy@videoelephant.com](mailto:privacy@videoelephant.com). We will respond to your request to change, correct, or delete your information within a reasonable timeframe and notify you of the action we have taken. 

###  How is your Information used? 

In general, Personal Data is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in providing our services. We use Personal Data in the following ways: 

  * To provide our services to you, as requested by you. 
  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you. 
  * If you are a registered Member on our site we will periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that promote our site or services as well as products or services we think you may be interested in. When you receive such promotional newsletters or communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving them from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service related communication, including notices of any updates to our Website Terms of Use or Privacy Policy. 
  * We may use financial information or payment method to process payment for any purchases, subscriptions or sales made on our website, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business. 

### Disclosure of your information

We will not rent, sell, or share your Personal Data with other people or non-affiliated companies except to the extent necessary to provide the site or services or unless we have your consent. For instance, we may share your Personal Data with a contracted third party service providers to support us offering our services, fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, conduct quality assurance testing, and/or to provide other services to VideoElephant. These third party service providers are required not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by us and are required to comply fully with the relevant data protection legislation. 

We may disclose Personal Data to third parties: 

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. 
  * If VideoElephant or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. 
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of business and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of VideoElephant , our customers, or others. 

We may provide data that does not identify any individual to third parties, where such information is combined with similar data. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit our site, the demographic breakdown of users of the applications on our site, or other activities of visitors on our website. Such third parties may include potential or actual advertisers, providers of advertising services, commercial partners, sponsors, and other similar parties. [[1]]()

### Where do we store your personal data?

The data, including Personal Data, that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of our Services. 

By submitting Personal Data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Acts. 

### How do we make sure your information is safe?

We will take all reasonable technical and organisational measures to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of Personal Data. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure (password and fire-wall) protected servers or servers hosted by third party service provider, any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Other than as stated above, we restrict access to Personal Data to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know such information in order to operate, develop or improve our site or services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination of their contract of employment or services agreement and/or criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

### Third party websites

Our site and services may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers, affiliates or social media websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. We encourage that you check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

### How do I access my information?

The Acts give you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Acts. Any access request may be subject to a fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

### User-Generated Content

We do not screen, filter or monitor user submissions to our website, nor do we scrape or glean personal information from any such submissions. However, to the extent that any video, comment or other user submission contains personal information (whether name, likeness, address, telephone number or otherwise, and whether such information pertains to the submitter or someone else), such personal information may be viewed by other users of the website. 

### User Submissions

We may provide areas on our site where you can post comments or reviews of content found on the Website. Such postings are governed by our Website  Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information. 

### Changes to our privacy policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Data, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Site. 

### Contact

Questions, comments, complaints and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [privacy@videoelephant.com](mailto:privacy@videoelephant.com).
